creattor.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | creaTTor.com

creaTTor is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains our data processing practices and your options regarding the ways in which your personal data is used. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to our processing please contact us.

##  INFORMATION COLLECTED

creaTTor collects the details provided by you on registration together with information we learn about you from your use of our Service and your visits to our website and other sites accessible from them. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site use which enables us to improve our service.

##  HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED

We will use your information to provide and personalise our service and to detect and prevent copyright infringement. We will also use your contact details to communicate with you. We may use your information to send you offers and news about creaTTor services or products, to customize content available on creaTTor, to conduct research for internal purposes and to use such information to improve our services and creaTTor website.

##  HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION COLLECTED

Except as noted below, creaTTor does not share your information with third parties.

We will disclose your information when required by law or under the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to conform to applicable law, comply with subpoenas, court orders or legal process served on creaTTor, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, and to protect the property or interests of creaTTor, its agents and employees, personal safety, or the public.

##  COOKIES

"Cookies" are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. creaTTor uses cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users, to help ensure the authenticity of registered users and to enable traffic monitoring.  
Non-registered visitors of the site are sent anonymous cookies to keep track of their browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile.  
Whilst you do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies in order to browse much of our web site or to access many of our services, you must have cookies enabled if you wish to access any areas reserved for registered users.  
Most browsers allow you to turn off the cookie function. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. As described above this will restrict the creaTTor services you can use.

##  OTHER WEBSITES

Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

##  PUBLICLY POSTED INFORMATION

If you register as a member of creaTTor and make postings as comments or on your user page, please remember that anything you post is publicly available. The user name you have chosen during the registration process is visible to all users of creaTTor. Your user page might show certain statistics regarding your use of creaTTor, such as the date you became a member, how long ago you last visited creaTTor, the categories of assets you have posted. Your user profile, and the information you choose to include in your profile, will also be available to other users and visitors that access your personal user page. creaTTor does not control, and is not responsible for, the use of any information or content that you have exposed to the public through your use of creaTTor.
